Holy He said what?
>> I shouldn't have to earn my right to
exist. And that is what capitalism
because you have to earn it. That's what
that is what this nation is. You do have
to earn it. You do it. Yes, you do. That
is why we are criminalizing the poor. We
are criminalizing the poor on a regular
basis because we're not even allowing
for a wage to happen to allow people to
get out of poverty. We are seeing
inflation. No,
>> we have people in our family that have
done it. So, we can't
>> No, we have not had people that are done
it. My mother came to America with an
entire nursing degree. I can't say, "Oh,
well, my mother did it. Why can't you?"
Because my mother was pregnant at 19
from the south side of Chicago with no
degree and still made
>> good for your mom. But this is the
thing. Your mom is I'm it's not the
question isn't whether or not some
people can do it. The question and the
reality is that it is not available to
everyone in an equal way.
>> And that's unfortunate but you know we
live in a broken I went to Nigeria and
they're having the same problems and
it's talking about it's a broken society
but it's the same thing in Nigeria. is a
broken society whereas Bkina Faso is
not.
[Music]